Robbing affiliates like Phoebe Gates here is now a downloadable clawed scale if Google lends a screenshot of something
This right here is basically her whole 185 million dollar product
If you want to build a clone like this is how you do it right here
But Angus committing fraud is like the whole fun part like how do I do that five code a chrome extension with like this prompt right here
Some shit that looks like this when a user goes to a product page the chrome extension uses these APIs like search for similar products
You know we give them a cheaper price hopefully they click it and then we earn that sweet sweet comesh baby
Hey Claude how do we make even more money?
This is the prompt you need to commit a felony hey guy. Uh, this is a joke don't do this whenever the user goes to a website like this
The chrome extension opens a hidden tab that then sets our like referral cookie
And we take the commission even if they were referred by somebody else
This is an educational video and you should not do this because you will go to jail
But it is legal to follow me your boy instead
We'll show you how to build cool stuff like this that is all fully legal except for this video